<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lentils on Yummy Collection</title>
    <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/tags/lentils/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lentils on Yummy Collection</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Sören Schneider</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 22:01:32 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/tags/lentils/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lentil Salad</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/lentil-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 22:01:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/lentil-salad/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (2 persons)  100g lentils (green or brown) handful of cherry tomatoes 1-2 spring onions optional: feta  For the sauce:  1 ts honey 1,5 Tbsp olive oil 1,5 Tbsp balsamico mustard a squirt of lemon juice  Instructions  Add lentils to water, bring to boil, simmer for around 20m-30m In the meantime, quarter all cherry tomatoes, chop spring onions to rings Mix the ingredients for the sauce After the lentils are done, add everything together, add salt &amp;amp; pepper  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweetpotatoe Curry</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/sweetpotatoe-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 21:53:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/sweetpotatoe-curry/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  500g sweetpotatoes, diced 1 pepperbell, diced 200g red lentils 2 medium-sized onions, diced 2 garlic cloves, minced 400ml coconut milk 250ml water 3 Tbsp tomato paste 1 can of diced tomatoes 3 ts curry powder 3 ts turmeric 3 ts garam masala 1 ts cumin a pinch of nutmeg  Instructions  Heat up pot, add oil, saute onions and garlic Add spices, stir until fragrant Add sweetpotatoes, pepperbell and lentils Deglaze with water, coconut milk and tomatoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dal Lemon Rice</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/dal-lemon-rice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 13:03:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/dal-lemon-rice/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Dal  300g yellow lentils 2 cloves garlic (1 finely chopped, 1 crushed) 1/2 white onion, finely chopped 2 ts turmeric 2 ts cumin seeds (1 of them crushed) 3/4 tsp ground ginger 1 ts ground coriander 1 ts curry powder 1 ts crushed chilis 200g chopped tomatoes 700ml vegetable stock ~10 curry leaves (optional)  Rice  Basmati rice 1 lemon 1 ts mustard seeds 1 ts crushed chilis 1/2 ts ground ginger 1 ts turmeric  Instructions Dal  Add lentils, crushed garlic, crushed cumin, turmeric, ginger, coriander, curry powder, chillies, chopped tomatoes and curry leaves to slow cooker Add stock, set on HIGH for 2 hours Fry cumin seeds and chopped garlic in 2 tbsp sunflower oil until garlic has browned and cumin is fragrant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oriental Lentil Soup</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/oriental-lentil-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 10:46:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/oriental-lentil-soup/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  2 onions, minced 1 clove garlic, minced 2 carrots, minced 2 Tbsp olive oil 1 chili (or alternatively 1 Tbsp thai curry paste) 1½ Tbsp cumin 100g dried apricots, finely chopped 250g red lentils 1 can of tomatoes, in pieces 1,2l vegetable stock salt, pepper  To serve  lemon juice yogurt parsley, chopped  Instructions  Sauté onions, garlic and carrots with oil in a pot Add the rest of the ingredients except for the salt Cook until the lentils are done (for slowcookers: HIGH ~4h, LOW: ~8h) Serve with lemon juice, a bit of yogurt and parsley  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lentil Curry</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/lentil-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 15:54:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/lentil-curry/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  1 sweet potatoe 2 carrots 300g beluga lentils 250g fresh spinach 1 onion 1 garlic clove 1 piece of ginger (thumb sized) 1 tb red curry paste 1 can of diced tomatoes 1 can of coconut milk ~500ml vegetable broth juice of a lime koriander  Instructions:  Dice onion, garlic and ginger. Cut carrots to discs. Heat a pot, add oil and cook for the diced vegetables for 2m.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dal Bhat</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/dal-bhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 23:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/dal-bhat/</guid>
      <description>Dal Ingredients  250g brown lentils (no need to soak) 1/2 ts salt 1/2 ts turmeric (turmeric) 1 medium onion, diced 2 tomatoes, diced 2 ts of cumin seeds (cumin) 2 tbsp butter  Instructions  Wash the lentils thoroughly in cold water twice in a large saucepan, drain They should be evenly distributed on the bottom of the pot Add enough water to the pot so that a little more than 1 1/2 phalanges of the ring finger are in the water above the lentils Add turmeric, bring the lentils to the boil and simmer over low heat The lentals should always be covered with a little water, do not stir Meanwhile, heat the butter in a pan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lentil Soup</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/lentil-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 00:34:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/lentil-soup/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  250g lentals 3-4 rather big potatoes 1 big carrot 1 cellerie 1 onion 0.5 leek 4 wiener sausages cumin parsley 2 bay leaves  For seasoning:
 Vinegar Nutmeg  Instructions  Chop the onion and the leek Chop the potatoes, carrot and cellerie into equally sized pieces Add the lentals to the crockpot and fill water just until the lentals are covered Cook for 4-5 hours on level high (Optional) 20 minutes before the time is up: If desired, mash the soup ingredients 20 minutes before the time&amp;rsquo;s up, start chopping the wieners and pour them into the soup.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
