<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>asian on Yummy Collection</title>
    <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/tags/asian/</link>
    <description>Recent content in asian on Yummy Collection</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Sören Schneider</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 23:21:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/tags/asian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dal Bhat</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/dal-bhat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 23:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/dal-bhat/</guid>
      <description>Dal Ingredients  250g brown lentils (no need to soak) 1/2 ts salt 1/2 ts turmeric (turmeric) 1 medium onion, diced 2 tomatoes, diced 2 ts of cumin seeds (cumin) 2 tbsp butter  Instructions  Wash the lentils thoroughly in cold water twice in a large saucepan, drain They should be evenly distributed on the bottom of the pot Add enough water to the pot so that a little more than 1 1/2 phalanges of the ring finger are in the water above the lentils Add turmeric, bring the lentils to the boil and simmer over low heat The lentals should always be covered with a little water, do not stir Meanwhile, heat the butter in a pan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Pumpkin Chickpea Curry</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/indian-pumpkin-chickpea-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 11:41:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/indian-pumpkin-chickpea-curry/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1 small onion, finely diced 800g red kuri squash, in small dices 2 carrots, small discs 400g chickpeas (not dried) 1 clove garlic 1 ts ginger, finely chopped 1 Tbsp curry powder 1 pinch of chili powder 1 can coconut milk 500ml vegetable stock 100g red lentils salt coriander Optional: 4 Tbsp mango chutney  Instructions  Add the ingredients in the above order (the liquids should now just cover the ingredients) Simmer for about 3-4 hours on the highest level or until the pumpkin pieces are quite soft Now add the dried lentils and continue to simmer for about 2 hours on LOW The dish is ready when the pumpkin is soft as butter and everything has a creamy consistency  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Korean Cucumber Salad</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/korean-cucumber-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 11:18:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/korean-cucumber-salad/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 Servings
 1 big cucumber 1 Tbsp salt 2 cloves garlic 1 spring onion 1 Tbsp soy sauce 2 Tbsp rice vinegar 1 tabespoon sugar 1 tabespoon sesame seeds 1 ts chili flakes 1 ts sesame oil  Instructions  Wash cucumber, remove skin if desired. Cut it to small pieces and put it in a bowl with 1 Tbsp of salt and leave it for 20m Roast sesame seeds in a frying pan without any oil Chop spring onion and cut garlic and add with all the other ingredients in a bowl Wash the cucumber thouroughly, there should be no salt left Add the cucumber to the bowl, sprinkle with the roasted sesame seeds  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Chua</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/do-chua/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 11:29:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/do-chua/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  500g carrots 500g radish 100g sugar 2 ts of salt 250ml luke warm water 250ml vinegar (5%) containers  Instructions  Peel the carrots and radish. Then cut into 5x0.5 cm long pieces Put the vegetable pieces in a bowl, add salt and mix well with your hands Mix vinegar with sugar and lukewarm water well until the sugar has completely dissolved The effect of the salt makes the carrots and radish pliable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tofu/Lemongrass Banh Mi</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/banh-mi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 11:27:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/banh-mi/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: For the tofu  500 gr tofu 2 EL lemongrass, minced 1-2 garlic cloves, minced 1 ts salt 2 Tbsp sugar pepper 1 chili, minced 4 Tbsp vegetable oil  The bread  baguette do chua mayonnaise coriander cucumber  Instructions:  Cut tofu in 1cm wide slices Mix lemon grass, garlic, salt, sugar, pepper, chili and oil Dry the tofu using a towel Rub in both sides of the tofu and let it rest for 15m.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garlic Sesame Noodles</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/garlic-sesame-noodles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 13:22:55 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/garlic-sesame-noodles/</guid>
      <description>Servings 2 Servings
Ingredients  4 bunches of ramen noodles 2 Tbsp vegetable oil 1 Tbsp sesame oil 3 cloves of garlic 1 thumb sized piece of ginger 2 ts sugar 1 Tbsp Sriracha sauce 60ml soy sauce 2 stalks of spring onions 200g broccoli  Instructions  Cook noodles according to instructions Peel and mince garlic and ginger, cut the spring onion Steam the broccoli Heat up a pan using the vegetable oil and saute the garlic and ginger Add sugar, sriracha and soy sauce, mix everything Turn down heat and wait until sauce becomes sticky Add noodles, spring onions and broccoli Add sesame oil, serve  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Butter Chicken</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/indian-butter-chicken/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 00:42:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/indian-butter-chicken/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  600g chicken breast 1 can coconut milk 70g tomato paste 1-2 tb curry paste 1 onion 2 garlic cloves ginger, thumb-sized 2tb butter 2tb yoghurt  Spices  curry powder kurkuma 1tb garam masala chili powder  Steps  Chop the onion, garlic and ginger into small bits, add to the bottom of the pot Chop the chicken into bite-sized pieces, add to the pot Add the rest of the ingredients to the pot, stir well Cook for 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naan</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/naan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 00:10:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/naan/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1/2 block of yeast 2 tb of sugar 150ml milk, room temperature 500g flour 150g yoghurt 1 ts baking powder 1 egg  For garlic Naan  2 cloves of garlic Butter  Instructions  Pour the milk into a bowl, add 1/2 Tbsp sugar and yeast. Stir for a bit. Leave it alone for 20 minutes so that the yeast is dissvoled Once the 20 minutes are over, get another big bowl and put a pinch of salt and the rest of the sugar (1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Curry</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/indian-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 23:56:16 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/indian-curry/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  One onion Two garlic cloves Ginger of the size of your thumb 800g red kuri squash, chopped into small pieces 2 carrots, chopped into small pieces 1 can chickpeas 4 Tbsp of mango chutney 1 can of coconut milk around 500ml water Optional: 150g lentils  Spices  Curry powder (White) pepper Coriander Chili powder One bay leave  Instructions  Chop and add onion, garlic and ginger to the crockpot Add all the ingredients in the order of their appearance to the pot Cook for 3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
