<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fast on Yummy Collection</title>
    <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/tags/fast/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fast on Yummy Collection</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Sören Schneider</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 14:19:44 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/tags/fast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Spätzle</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/sp%C3%A4tzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 14:19:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/sp%C3%A4tzle/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Serves 4 people
 400g flour 4 medium sized eggs 1 ts salt 220ml cold water  Instructions  Heat up a big pot of salted water Mix all ingredients well until bubbles in the dough appear Put the spätzle in the boiling water Once they appear on the surface they&amp;rsquo;re cooked  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doriyaki</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/doriyaki/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 10:03:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/doriyaki/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients:  2 eggs 20g sugar 2 Tbsp honey 1/2 ts Vanilla extract 90g flour 1 ts baking powder 10 ml water  Instructions:  Add eggs, sugar, honey and vanilla in a bowl and stir until the sugar is dissolved Add flour, baking powder, water and whisk it Leave for 10m Set stove to low heat and add dough, when bubbles appear, flip  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Korean Cucumber Salad</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/korean-cucumber-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 11:18:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/korean-cucumber-salad/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 Servings
 1 big cucumber 1 Tbsp salt 2 cloves garlic 1 spring onion 1 Tbsp soy sauce 2 Tbsp rice vinegar 1 tabespoon sugar 1 tabespoon sesame seeds 1 ts chili flakes 1 ts sesame oil  Instructions  Wash cucumber, remove skin if desired. Cut it to small pieces and put it in a bowl with 1 Tbsp of salt and leave it for 20m Roast sesame seeds in a frying pan without any oil Chop spring onion and cut garlic and add with all the other ingredients in a bowl Wash the cucumber thouroughly, there should be no salt left Add the cucumber to the bowl, sprinkle with the roasted sesame seeds  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Cream</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/ice-cream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 14:32:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/ice-cream/</guid>
      <description>One of Ben &amp;amp; Jerry&amp;rsquo;s basic ice cream receipes.
Ingredients  2 large eggs 125g cup sugar 400ml heavy/whipping cream 200ml milk  Instructions  Whisk the eggs until light and fluffy for about 1-2m Whisk in the sugar, a little at a time, continue whisking until it&amp;rsquo;s completely blended. Keep going for about 1 minute more Pour in the cream and milk and whisk to blend  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flammkuchen / tarte flambée</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/flammkuchen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 11:25:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/flammkuchen/</guid>
      <description>Servings Produces 2 Flammkuchen
Ingredients:  200g flour 1 ts salt 2 Tbsp oil 110ml water  Instructions:  Mix all the ingredients in a bowl Knead them for 3 minutes  Variations:  Gratinée: with Gruyère cheese Forestière: with mushrooms Sweet: dessert version with apples and cinnamon, flambéed with Calvados  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
