<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dessert on Yummy Collection</title>
    <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/tags/dessert/</link>
    <description>Recent content in dessert on Yummy Collection</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Sören Schneider</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 12:48:25 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/tags/dessert/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Matcha Mascarpone Pots</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/matcha-mascarpone-pots/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 12:48:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/matcha-mascarpone-pots/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 4-6 servings
 2 Tbsp full fat milk 1 Tbsp matcha, plus a little extra for dusting 1 Tbsp vanilla extract / seeds from 1 vanilla pod 500g mascarpone at room temperature 75g creme fraiche 75g sugar pinch of salt  Instructions  Whisk milk and matcha until the lumps are gone Add all the other ingredients Whisk until everything is smooth, then keep whisking to thicken Sprinkle a bit matcha on top for decoration  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiramisu</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/tiramisu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 09:30:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/tiramisu/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  4 fresh eggs Savoiardi biscuits 300g (&amp;ldquo;ladyfingers&amp;rdquo;) Mascarpone 500g Sugar 75g Cacao powder Coffee  Instructions  Separate yolks from egg whites in two different bowls (medium size) Add half of the sugar to the yolks and whip them until they become like a cream, then add the mascarpone Now whip the egg whites - pouring the remaining sugar a little at a time - until stiff Add them to the yolks cream, stirring slowly without changing direction Prepare a coffee pot (two medium mokas are enough), spread a little cream in a baking tray and start placing the biscuits soaked in coffee (tip: do not soak them too much - they shouldn’t melt).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hazelnutcake</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/hazelnutcake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 10:38:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/hazelnutcake/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: For the bottom:  70g butter 120g sugar 1 packet vanilla sugar 5 eggs (eiweiß zu schnee schlagen) 140g ground hazelnuts 3 tbsp flour 2 spoon baking soda  For the topping: topping:  1/2 package cream. whip it! 1 package cream stiffener  Instructions:  After baking the bottom, crumble a hole from the center of the bottom, leave the border Add the crumbles to the topping and re-fill the center Add some chocolate sprinkles Coat the border with melted chocolate  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coconut Icecream</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/coconut-ice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 12:38:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/coconut-ice/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  400ml coconut milk 100ml water 150ml cream 100g sugar 50g coconut flakes 3 egg yolks  Steps  Cook the coconut milk with the water, let it cool back down Stir egg yolk with sugar until creamy and add coconut flakes Add the cooled down coconut milk to the eggs and mix it well Put everything back to the pot with medium heat to thicken it slightly Let it cool down a bit, stir in the cream Put it in the fridge until cold, then put it to the ice machine  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salt Caramel Cream</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/salt-caramel-cream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 14:44:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/salt-caramel-cream/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  200g sugar 90g butter in cubes 120ml cream 1-2 ts sea salt  Instructions  Add sugar with a bit of water in a wide pot with a thick bottom. Use medium heat until the sugar turns to golden caramel. Don&amp;rsquo;t leave it for too long, it will turn bitter Carefully give the butter cubes to the caramel (it&amp;rsquo;s probably going to splash) Give the cream and whisk thorughly until the caramel is dissolved Add the salt to the pot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Cream</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/ice-cream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 14:32:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/ice-cream/</guid>
      <description>One of Ben &amp;amp; Jerry&amp;rsquo;s basic ice cream receipes.
Ingredients  2 large eggs 125g cup sugar 400ml heavy/whipping cream 200ml milk  Instructions  Whisk the eggs until light and fluffy for about 1-2m Whisk in the sugar, a little at a time, continue whisking until it&amp;rsquo;s completely blended. Keep going for about 1 minute more Pour in the cream and milk and whisk to blend  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Banana Chocolate Bread</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/banana-chocolate-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 00:21:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/banana-chocolate-bread/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  220g flour 1 pinch of salt 0.5 Tbsp baking soda 0.5 Tbsp baking powder 75g chopped dark chocolate 50g hazelnut or walnut 75g butter 75g sugar 2 eggs 2 ripe bananas  Steps  Add the eggs, sugar, butter and bananas to a bowl, use a mixer or fork to create a evenly mass. Add all other ingredients to another bowl, mix and stir everything. Add the paste from step one.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
