<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>side-dish on Yummy Collection</title>
    <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/tags/side-dish/</link>
    <description>Recent content in side-dish on Yummy Collection</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Sören Schneider</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 11:18:39 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/tags/side-dish/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Korean Cucumber Salad</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/korean-cucumber-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 11:18:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/korean-cucumber-salad/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 Servings
 1 big cucumber 1 Tbsp salt 2 cloves garlic 1 spring onion 1 Tbsp soy sauce 2 Tbsp rice vinegar 1 tabespoon sugar 1 tabespoon sesame seeds 1 ts chili flakes 1 ts sesame oil  Instructions  Wash cucumber, remove skin if desired. Cut it to small pieces and put it in a bowl with 1 Tbsp of salt and leave it for 20m Roast sesame seeds in a frying pan without any oil Chop spring onion and cut garlic and add with all the other ingredients in a bowl Wash the cucumber thouroughly, there should be no salt left Add the cucumber to the bowl, sprinkle with the roasted sesame seeds  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mexican Salsa</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/salsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 11:38:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/salsa/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  5 tomatoes, peeled 2 red bell pepper 2 green bell pepper 3 medium-large onion 2 chilli pepper juice of 1 lemon 1 Tbsp salt 2 Tbsp sugar  Instructions  Chop everything Put the diced ingredients in a saucepan without a lid and cook over medium heat for about 1-1,5 hours, until the salsa has a creamy substance Stir often  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Chua</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/do-chua/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 11:29:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/do-chua/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  500g carrots 500g radish 100g sugar 2 ts of salt 250ml luke warm water 250ml vinegar (5%) containers  Instructions  Peel the carrots and radish. Then cut into 5x0.5 cm long pieces Put the vegetable pieces in a bowl, add salt and mix well with your hands Mix vinegar with sugar and lukewarm water well until the sugar has completely dissolved The effect of the salt makes the carrots and radish pliable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naan</title>
      <link>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/naan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 00:10:12 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yummy.soerenschneider.com/receipes/naan/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients  1/2 block of yeast 2 tb of sugar 150ml milk, room temperature 500g flour 150g yoghurt 1 ts baking powder 1 egg  For garlic Naan  2 cloves of garlic Butter  Instructions  Pour the milk into a bowl, add 1/2 Tbsp sugar and yeast. Stir for a bit. Leave it alone for 20 minutes so that the yeast is dissvoled Once the 20 minutes are over, get another big bowl and put a pinch of salt and the rest of the sugar (1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
